I don't know.
我不知道
Maybe we were doomed from the beginning.
也许我们一开始就被诅咒了
I mean,it's not like Dad was Mr. Sunshine.
我是说 也许爸爸压根儿就不是什么"阳光先生"
Sometimes I think all our problems came directly from him.
有时候 我觉得我们所有的问题都来源于他
But a lot of the good stuff did,too.
但他也带来了很多好的一面
Remember what he always called us?
还记得他怎么叫我们的嘛
The Gruesome Twosome.
"可怕二人组"
He told us to stick together,no matter what.
他告诉我们 不管发生什么都要在一起
God! What the hell happened to us?
天啊 我们到底是怎么了
片名：失魂姐弟
Hello?
喂
Hi,is this Maggie Dean?
嗨 你是马吉·迪恩吗
Yes.
是的
This is L.A. Presbyterian Hospital.
我这里是洛杉矶长老会医院
You know,I'm on the National Do Not Call Registry.
我已经隐藏了自己的号码了啊
How did you get this number?
你还怎么知道我号码的
I'm calling to inform you that your brother Milo
我打给你是通知你你弟弟麦洛
was admitted this afternoon after an attempted suicide.
今天下午被发现自杀未遂
He's okay.
他没事了
Ms. Dean?
迪恩小姐？
Yes.
嗯
- He's okay. - Good,thank you.
- 他没事了 - 好的 谢谢你
It's a good thing he was blasting his music.
幸好当时他音乐开的很大声
A neighbor complained and got the building manager.
然后邻居很烦 于是找到了物管人员
Here's his note.
这是他留的字条
"To whom it may concern..."
敬启者
Jesus.
天啊
When was the last time you saw each other?
你们俩上次见面是什么时候了
About 10 years.
10年了吧
Hey,Milo.
嘿 麦洛
Hey.
嘿
You changed your hair.
你换发型了
Oh,yeah. It's...
哦 是的…
It's been light for a while,I guess.
这样看着清爽些
Look at you.
看看你呀
Yeah,look at me.
是啊 瞧瞧我
Another tragic gay cliché.
又一个悲剧发生了
I don't know if you still like apple fritters.
我不知道 你还喜不喜欢炸苹果饼
Probably not as good as Jensen's.
不过可能没延森那家做的好吃
I'm not really hungry.
我不是很饿
I'll just leave them here.
放这里了
How many days did they say you have to be in here?
他们说你得在这里待几天？
A day or two.
一两天吧
Do you have anyone...
你有…
Do you live alone?
你一个人住吗
Yeah,I live alone.
是的 一个人住
Well,I'm around the next couple days,if you need anything.
好吧 我最近都在 这如果你需要我帮什么的话…
Maggie,this was just some stupid thing I did.
马吉 这是我做的一件蠢事
I was drunk and feeling melodramatic,so...
我当时喝多了觉得人生如戏所以…
You didn't have to come here.
你其实可以不用来的
You should go.
你应该离开
Hey.
嘿
They told me you were down here.
他们跟我说你在这里
I get discharged today.
我今天出院
They just called me a cab. I thought you were going home.
他们刚给找叫了辆出租车 我以为你要回家呢
Why,because you told me to?
为什么 就因为你说让我回去我就回去？
No,because I asked you to.
不 是因为我请你回去
What,are you king of the hospital now?
什么 你是医院一霸了？
Have you read Marley and Me?
你读过吗《马利和我》？
Yeah,sad.
读过 悲剧
Why is it sad?
为什么是悲剧
You don't know what happens?
你不知道发生了什么吗
No,that's why I'm reading it.
不知道 所以我才想读
Oh,sorry.
噢 抱歉
- What? - Nothing.
- 什么 - 没什么
- What,does the dog die at the end? - No,I didn't say that.
- 什么 狗最后死掉了吗 - 没有 我可没有说
The fucking dog dies at the end.
那狗最后肯定死了
- I didn't... I'm not saying anything. - Look how much I had left.
- 我没 我没有说什么啊 - 我仅剩的已经不多了
I'm sorry I ruined it.
很抱歉 我剧透了
Maggie,I know the dog dies.
马吉 我知道那狗死了
Everyone knows the dog dies.
大家都知道
It's the book where the dog dies.
那狗就是死在书里的
Asshole.
可恶
I see you're getting your sense of humor back.
看来你又找回了自己的幽默感了啊
Yeah,they can't take that away from me.
是啊 这一点他们是剥夺不走的
I was thinking,
我在想
maybe you'd wanna come stay with me?
你要不要来跟我一起住
What,back to New York?
什么回纽约？
Yeah. I mean just for a little bit,until you feel better.
是的 我是说就一阵子 直到你好些了 再…
I have a guest room and you can meet Lance finally.
我有客房 你也终于可以见到兰斯了
Nyack's really beautiful this time of year.
每年这时候奈亚克都是最漂亮的
So the crack team of hospital crisis counselors got to you,too,huh?
这么说 医院的辅导员也找你聊过了吧？
- This was my decision. - Yeah,whatever.
- 不 这是我的决定 - 是啊 无所谓了
They guilted you into this.
他们是用你的内疚心说服你的
You're right. It's probably a bad idea.
也许你说的对 我就不该说这个
Hey,Maggie.
嘿 马吉
I have an aquarium
我有个鱼缸
full of very beloved,fat goldfish.
全是可爱的肥金鱼
You can get new goldfish in New York.
你可以去纽约了再买新的
Welcome home.
欢迎回家
Hey,here he is.
嘿 他来了
- Lance. - Yeah,sure am.
- 兰斯 - 嗯 没错儿
- How are ya? - Great to meet you.
- 你还好吗 - 很高兴见到你
Oh,shit. Sorry,man.
噢 该死 抱歉 伙计
It's okay. Don't worry about it. They're healing over,so it's fine.
没事的别担心 在慢慢愈合没事的
I'm so psyched to finally meet you,you know?
终于见到你 真是兴奋
Yeah,you,too.
是的 我也是
Mysterious Milo in the flesh,right?
亲眼见到神秘的麦洛 没错吧
Well,actually,I'm clothed now,so you'll have to get to know me
嗯 我现在穿着衣服的 所以你想亲眼见到"整个麦洛"的话
a little bit better before you see me in the flesh.
你还得先多了解点我才行
Cool,cool.
好 很好
Well,hey,if you need anything,I'm around,so don't hesitate to holler.
嘿 如果有需要叫我 我随时都在的 不用担心
I'm just... I'm doing a few chores.
我反正 手里事情也不多
I will,I will,thank you. Thanks for having me.
我会的 谢谢你 谢谢您的款待
Okay,take it easy,amigo.
好的 慢慢来 朋友
You,too,amigo.
你也是 朋友
Jesus,Maggie.
天啊 马吉
So,Milo,you hear about your wild and crazy sister?
那么 麦洛 你听说过你姐姐的疯狂事迹没有
Are you... He doesn't know?
你… 他不知道吗
Your wild and crazy sister has been taking...
你这姐姐啊…
Give me a drumroll. Come on,drumroll. Come on,louder.
来一个 敲大声点儿 敲大声点儿
Scuba diving lessons.
她在学潜水
- Yeah. - Doesn't that sound like fun?
- 是 - 有意思吗
Yeah,if you like scuba diving,yeah.
是啊 如果你喜欢的话 那应该还挺有意思的
I do.
我喜欢的
She's preparing for our tropical Hawaiian honeymoon.
她是在为我们的夏威夷蜜月做准备呢
It's gonna be badass.
肯定很好玩
Honeymoon?
蜜月？
Better two years late than never. It was her idea. it was your idea.
晚两年也比没有的好 是她主意 是你的主意
- Better late than never. - Yeah.
- 有总比没有好 - 是啊
She's always getting crazy ideas.
她总是会有这么些点子
Last month,it was salsa dancing. Have you ever heard of salsa dancing?
上个月 她还在学萨尔萨舞 你听说过萨尔萨舞蹈吗
It's kind of like a Spanish-flavored dancing?
是种西班牙风情的舞蹈
Yeah,yeah,the... Yeah.
是 是
- So now it's scuba diving. - Yeah.
- 现在又学轻便潜水 - 是啊
You ever been?
你学过吗
- No,no. - No?
- 没 没有 - 没有？
- Dude,you'd love it. It's awesome. - Right.
- 伙计你会喜欢的 简直帅呆了 - 是啊
Me and my buddy Craig,a couple years ago,we went to Costa Rica.
我和我朋友克雷格 几年前一起去了哥斯达黎加
This was before Maggie was on the scene.
那还是马吉出现在我生活里之前
PM,Pre-Maggie.
叫PM时期 也就是"马吉前期"
And the first time we go out on a dive,
第一次我们一起出去潜水
we saw an effing sea turtle,which is very rare.
我们看到了个该死的海龟 很稀有的
- Incredibly rare. - I think it's pretty normal,right?
- 绝世珍宝 - 我觉得海龟很常见吧
- Seeing sea turtles? - What?
- 看海龟不常见么 - 什么
When you're diving,seeing sea turtles? I think that's very...
潜水看到海龟很罕见吗？我觉得很…
No,I think you're thinking of just regular turtles
不 我知道你说的应该是普通的乌龟吧
that you'd see in,like,a pond or a stream.
就是池塘里那种
I'm talking about a sea turtle in the wild.
我说的是海龟 野生的
We were swimming so close to it that you could practically touch it.
我们就在它附近 几乎可以摸到它了
- Is it okay if I tell him? Can I? - Nothing really to tell yet.
- 我能告诉他吗 - 还不算什么大新闻啦
You ready for some big news?
你准备妤听了吗
- We're trying to get pregnant. - Really?
- 我们准备要一胎 - 真的吗
- We are trying to get pregnant. - Yeah.
- 我们准备要孩子了 - 是的
And I say "we are," because it's not sexist that way.
而我刚说的是"我们" 因为这样就不会显得性别歧视
- Right? That's what you told me. - Yeah.
- 对吧 你是这样教我的 - 是的
I thought you never wanted to have kids.
我还以为你永远不想要孩子呢
Well,I may have said that in high school or something,
好吧 那是我高中说的东西了吧
but obviously people change their minds on that.
但是很显然大家都会变得嘛
No,I... That's great.
不 我 很好
I love kids.
我喜欢小孩子
Except the fat ones.
除了胖的那些
Fuck those little turds,right?
去他妈的那些可恶的人 对吧？
He's kidding. He's being a smartass.
他开玩笑呢 他是想装聪明
- Don't mind him. - I'm messing with you.
- 别介意他 - 我跟你开玩笑的
I was like,"Whoa,what's this guy got against fat kids?"
我是还在想 "哇哦 这家伙为什么讨厌胖孩子"
- No,he's... - I mean,I was a fat kid.
- 不 他是… - 我还在想我就是个胖孩子
- Oh,you were? - I was built like a damn tank,yeah.
- 噢 是吗 - 我跟个坦克一样
- She's seen the pictures. - It's pretty cute,though.
- 她看过照片的 - 不过很可爱
I look like a... Just a little pillow with legs.
我看起来就像… 长了腿的枕头
- A little marshmallow. - Yeah.
- 棉花糖一样 - 是的
Hey,here's to you guys.
嘿 来祝你们两位
- Thanks. - May your kids be happy and fat.
- 谢谢 - 祝你们的孩子又快乐又胖胖
Cool,man,thanks.
谢啦 伙计
I mean,it hasn't happened yet,but we're definitely giving it a go.
虽然还没怀上 不过我们准备一试了
Well,keep trying,guys-
好的 努力试
I can't wait to be the creepy gay uncle.
我已经迫不及待的想做怪叔叔了
- You're hired. - Okay.
- 就选你了 - 好的
You got the job.
怪叔叔非你莫属
- Hey. - Hey.
- 嘿 - 嘿
- Settling in? - Yeah.
- 还习惯吧 - 嗯
No,yeah,it's like a Martha Stewart wonderland.
还可以吧有点像玛莎·斯图尔特的仙境
So,you met Lance.
那么你也见过兰斯了
Yeah,I met Lance.
是啊 见过了
Isn't he the best?
他难道不是最棒的吗
Yeah,he's like a big Labrador retriever.
我觉得他有点像拉布拉多寻回犬
Yeah,I guess.
是啊 也许吧
He's just the nicest guy on the planet.
他是这地球上最好的人了
I really lucked out.
我真的很幸运
Yeah,you're really going for it.
是啊 你真的试试
- What does that mean? - You're going for it.
- 什么意思 - 你得去试试
Just,like,the job,the house,the furniture. The Lance.
就像工作房子家具 还有兰斯
I guess I grew up.
我想我长大了
- So,what about you? - What about me?
- 那 你呢 - 我怎么了
Well,last I heard,you moved to L.A. to be an actor?
上次我听说你搬到洛杉矶 是为了当演员？
That was,like,10 years ago?
那是10年前的事情了吧
- Yeah,did you not hear'? I won an Oscar. -Oh,very funny.
- 是啊 你没听说吗我还获了奥斯卡奖 - 噢 很有意思
Yeah,I played a retarded Ukrainian immigrant
是啊 我扮演的白痴乌克兰移民
who inspires a bunch of school kids in Brooklyn by playing chess.
通过下棋的方式 激励了布鲁克林一群在校生
- Seriously. - Seriously,
- 真的 - 是真的
acting's kinda hard when you don't have an agent.
如果没有经纪人的话 演艺圈还是很难混的
- So... - Well,what are you doing for money?
- 所以… - 那你以什么谋生呢
Let me guess,male prostitute joke coming...
我猜猜 男妓笑话…
What do you want me to say,Maggie?
马吉 你想我说什么？
I wait tables at a shitty tourist restaurant in Hollywood.
我在好莱坞的一个旅游餐馆里当服务员
It's fucking boring,the end. What do you want to know?
到头来无聊到死 你想知道什么
You know,I'm tired. I'm gonna go to bed.
我累了 我要睡觉了
All right,good night.
好的 晚安
Shit.
该死
The key to buddy breathing is not to panic.
呼吸的关键 就在于不要慌张
Don't freak out or you'll die.
不要害怕 否则你就死了
Don't yank the regulator away from your partner.
不要把你伙伴的呼吸器拽走了
Don't bogart the thing either.
也不要绷得太紧
All right,so,everybody partner up. Let's go,let's do it.
好的 各位起来 开始了 来吧
Looking for a date?
想约吗
A partner.
约个搭档
Oh,yeah,sure. Okay.
哦 当然了
This is a book that we're selling a lot more of.
这是一本书 我们卖的更多
It's just much more practical. It's much more hands-on.
这个更加实用 更容易上手
- Does that sound... - it sounds perfect.
- 你觉得 - 挺好的
- Okay,good. Yeah,good luck. - Thank you.
- 好的 祝你好运 - 谢谢你
Surprise.
惊讶吧
Milo.
麦洛
Back from the dead.
鬼门关回来
What are you doing here?
你在这里干什么
I just rolled into town. I wanted to say hi.
我刚进城 我想过来打个招呼
No,what are you doing here at the store?
不 你来店里干什么的
I am looking for the new Danielle Steel novel.
我是来找丹尼尔·斯蒂尔的小说的
- You should go. - No,hey,no,I... Let's go hiking.
- 你快走吧 - 不 嘿 我们去走走吧
Let's go to Kate's Lazy Meadow and,you know,
我们去凯特莱兹牧场
- go to the Harvest Festival and... - Milo,you're out of your mind.
- 去看收获节… - 麦洛 你疯了
No,Rich,I just think...
不 里奇 我只是在想…
Don't come here again.
别再过来了
When do the boys show up?
男孩子们什么时候来
It's Dyke Night,sweetie.
这是 女同之夜 亲爱的
- It's what? - Dyke Night.
- 什么 - 女同性恋之夜
Dyke Night?
女同性恋之夜
I showed up on Dyke Night?
我在女同性恋之夜来这里？
Yeah.
是的
Shit.
该死
- Jesus. - Hey!
- 天啊 - 嘿
Cal's Corner,fucking Dyke Night.
卡尔酒吧 居然在搞女同夜
- What? - Oh,boy.
- 什么 - 噢 天啊
Dyke Night.
女同之夜
Milo,can we talk about this in the morning?
麦洛 我们能早上再说嘛
Sandra and Melissa were very nice.
桑德拉和梅利莎人都很好
They were two lesbian ladies who taught me how to play darts.
她们俩是同性恋 教我怎么玩飞镖
But they were not what I was looking for.
但那不是我想找的
What I was looking for,
我想找的是
and you should know this since we're now related,Lance,
兰斯而你应该知道 现在我们也算亲戚了
I was looking for some cock.
我其实是想找男人
Okay,Milo,enough.
够了 麦洛
You're fine 'cause you're married to my sister.
你很安全因为 你已经跟我姐姐在一起了
- You're off-limits. - "Off-limits."
- 我不会找你的 - "不会找我"
Just letting you know,if any of your little buddies around,just...
只是想让你知道 如果你有哪个朋友
- Milo! Go to bed. - I will be on them like steak on rice.
- 麦洛 睡觉去 - 我跟他们一起就像牛摊配米饭一样
Okay,Milo,good night.
好了 麦洛 晚安
I'm just letting you know. I'm a little tipsy. I'm sorry.
我只是让你知道我有点醉了 抱歉
- That's okay. - No shit.
- 没事的 - 别废话了
- Milo,good night. - Good night.
- 麦洛 晚安 - 晚安
- Yeah,about last night... - You can't do stuff like that.
- 是 昨晚的事情… - 你不能那样
Sorry,I was just trying to blow off some steam,that's all. I just...
抱歉 我只是… 想缓解下压力仅此而已…
So,Lance and I were talking,and he might need some help
那么 兰斯和我聊过了 他可能需要一些帮助
on this trail project at the dam.
就是大坝上的那个铁轨的项目
Just clearing brush and stuff.
收拾收拾东西 擦一擦什么的
A trail project at the dam?
大坝上的的铁轨项目？
Yeah. It's what he does.
是的 他就是做这个的
What do you mean,clearing brush? Like picking up sticks?
收拾东西是干什么 比如说捡捡垃圾？
Brush! Sticks and leaves and pieces of bushes and stuff.
清洁 就是地上的棍子啊 树叶什么的
- It might be good for you. - So,it's like a job?
- 这也许对你有好处 - 那 这是个工作咯？
It might be nice for you to spend time with him and stuff.
也许让你跟他在一起做做事 会有好处呢
Be out in nature with the brush.
接触大自然
Do I get a sexy outfit?
是不是还有性感的全套装备
I'll make sure of it.
这点我去确定
Here.
来
Probably should've worn longer sleeves.
也许应该穿个长袖衣服
Yeah,no,I mean,next time,you know?
是啊 我是说下次吧
'Cause then if you have long sleeves,you can make more of a scooping motion.
因为如果你袖子很长 你动作就可以更大一些了
You might be able to get more with each grab,you know?
这样一次也许可以抓的更多了
Yeah,no,I get it.
是的 我知道了
I'm not really an outdoorsy kind of guy.
我不是那种特别喜欢户外运动的人
Right. Well,no worries,my man.
嗯 不用担心 伙计
You know,I got an extra fleece in the truck.
我车上还有一些羊绒布
- You want me to go... - No,no,I'm good.
- 你想我去… - 不 不用 我挺好的
- Thank you. - You got it?
- 谢谢 - 你可以？
Oh,you gotta be fucking kidding me.
噢 不是吧
You okay? You all right?
你还好 没事吧
Take a breath. Take a breath.
呼吸 呼吸
What happened down there?
在下面干什么呢？
Nothing,I'm fine.
没什么 我没事
- Yeah? - I'm fine.
- 嗯？- 我没事
All right.
好的
Hello?
嗨
- Hi. - What the hell's that?
- 嗨 - 那是什么东西
Happy first day of work.
祝你第一天工作快乐
You didn't have to do that.
你不必这样的
What,you don't like it?
什么 你不喜欢吗？
No,I love it. It's great.
不 我很喜欢很棒
So,I told somebody that I was in town,
我今天跟个家伙说我进城了
and I didn't think she would come,so don't freak out.
我没想到她会来 所以别被吓到了
Hi,angel.
嗨 天使
Mother.
妈妈
Oh,dear.
噢 天啊
Okay,broken glass. Everybody freeze. I'm gonna go get a dustpan. You okay?
好的 碎玻璃 大家都别动 我去拿簸箕你没事吧
- Yeah. - I'm gonna go get a dustpan.
- 嗯 - 我去拿扫把
Okay.
好
- So,that's Tanner? - No,that's Tad.
- 那是坦纳？- 不是 塔德
Tanner's the oldest.
坦纳是最老的那个
They look a lot like their father.
他们看起来很像他们父亲
- See? - I love Arches.
- 看 - 我喜欢拱门
- Yeah. - The Grand Canyon's gotten so commercial.
- 是的 - 科罗拉多大峡谷
Arches has retained its essence,you know?
变得如此商业化而 拱门却保留了它的本质
It's just such a very,very spiritual place.
是个非常非常有精神的地方
Arches is rad.
拱门就是根本
I actually road-tripped it down there spring break sophomore year.
我之前大二春假 还去那边玩过
- It's insane. Unbelievable. - A toast? A toast? I want to make a toast.
- 不敢相信 太美了 - 干杯吗 干杯吗 我想干杯
To my beautiful,beautiful children,and to my lovely son-in-law.
致我美丽的孩子们 还有我的女婿
May the light embrace you with its energy infinite.
愿光芒拥抱你们给予无限的能量
May you dwell in a place of peace and tolerance.
愿你们住在一个平静宽容的地方
May you live in warmth and understanding for your days eternal.
愿你们住在温暖和包容你们的永恒世界里
- Amen. - Yeah.
- 阿门 - 嗯
- Cheers. - Now.
- 干杯 - 来
Darling,thank you.
亲爱的 谢谢你
So,when are you gonna come down and visit us in Sedona?
那 你们什么时候来塞多纳看我们
I guess whenever we're invited.
那要看啥时候邀请我们去
Oh,my God! You just have to show up.
哦 天啊 你们直接过来就好了
Just drop in. We don't like to be scheduled.
随时来 我们不喜欢安排时间
- Perfect. - Great,so how's next week?
- 很好 - 好 那不如下周吧？
Next... That's not gonna actually be the best week.
下… 下周 不是很合适吧
Okay,great. The week after that. We can go then.
好吧 很好 那就下下周我们可以去
Okay,well...
好的 这个…
Hey,Mom,how are the alpacas?
嘿 妈妈 羊驼都还好吗
We had to get rid of them. It was just too much poop.
我们不得不卖掉 它们便便太多了
You know what they say,everybody poops,right?
你知道他们说啥吗 大家都会拉屎的
When I was a kid,I didn't think that girls pooped.
我还是孩子的时候 我还以为女生不会拉屎
- Seriously. - I've never taken a shit before.
- 说真的 - 我以前就从没拉过
Milo.
麦洛
So what about your insight retreats,Mom?
妈 你的疗养还好吗
- What about them? - Do you have one coming up?
- 疗养怎么了 - 你有定时间吗
Why do you ask?
为什么这么问
Oh,I just want to make sure I don't schedule
哦 我只是想确定 我没有把我人生大事那天
the most important event of my life on the same day.
刚好定在了你要去疗养的那天
Okay,just...
好吧
You know it broke my heart to miss the wedding.
你知道 如果我错过婚礼了 我会很难道的
Actually,you know,I don't know that it did.
事实上 我还不知道你会觉得伤心
- You're here now,right? - Yes,yes. Thank you.
- 你都已经来了 对吧？- 是的 谢谢
Did everybody hear how I've never taken a shit before?
有人听过我以前怎么一直没拉过屎吗？
- Did you guys miss that? - Yeah.
- 你们错过了吧 - 是的
Why are we talking about such unpleasant things?
为什么我们要聊这么恶心的东西
Milo,what's new with you,darling?
麦洛 你又有什么新打算 亲爱的？
I'm gonna go grab the Tabasco.
我去拿点辣酱油
Anybody like anything?
还有人要什么吗
Everything's great.
都挺好的
- It's good. - That's terrific.
- 很好 - 那真是好极了
Everything is terrific.
一切都是极好的
Now,breathe out.
现在呼气
Yes.
没错
You're cleansed. Open your eyes.
你已经被净化了张开双眼吧
Oh,my God! How do you feel?
哦 天啊 你感觉怎么样
Good,yeah. I might be a little drunk.
很好 也许我有点喝醉了
You look completely different.
你看起来完全不一样
Oh,my God! There's just... There's a...
哦 我的天 你身上…
A purity and a kind of a glow coming off you.
有种纯净的光冒了出来
It's emanating from your crown chakra.
从你头上的皇冠上发出
Lance,would you like to be cleansed?
兰斯 你愿意被洗礼一下吗
I'm okay,thank you. I took a sauna this morning.
我没事的 谢谢你 我今天去洗过桑拿了
- But I feel good. - Sweetheart?
- 我感觉很好 - 亲爱的呢
Oh,I don't usually drink and cleanse.
噢 我不喝酒也不用被洗礼
Just,like,personal policy.
个人习惯吧
But thank you.
不过还是谢谢你
Okay,I guess I should be heading back.
好了 我想我该回家了
What,like,back to Arizona?
什么 回亚利桑那州吗？
Well,it's a terrific coincidence.
嗯 是非常巧
You know,Maggie,you asked me about the insight retreat.
马吉 你问我疗养的事情
Guess where it is this year?
猜猜今年是哪儿
Woodstock. Around the corner.
伍德斯托克 就那边不远
- Oh,you've gotta be kidding. - I mean,it's such a...
- 哦 真是不敢相信 - 我是说… 这不是
This just worked out perfectly.
安排的非常好
So that's why you came here?
所以你才来这里？
No,no.
不 不
I came here to see you two.
我是过来看你们俩的
Oh,just shut up,Mother.
噢 闭嘴吧 妈妈
- Hey,Maggie. - This is classic.
- 嘿 马吉 - 这已经是传统了
- Classic bullshit. - Okay,Maggie...
- 传统性的胡扯 - 好吧 马吉…
I have to compliment you,though. I really do.
其实我也很想称赞你 真的
You gave it a good shot.
你这样尝试是不错的
But I have to tell you,you're really not that good of an actress.
但是我不得不告诉你 你演技还是太差了点
- Okay. Well,as pleasant as this is... - Stop trying,Judy.
- 好吧 和这个有意思的… - 别挣扎了 朱迪
Stop trying-
别试了
There are worse things than being a shitty mother.
当个糟糕的妈妈 不算事最差的事情了
So,if you've finished
所以 如果你已经
vomiting all over me,
讨厌够我了
I will just say
那我就只说
thank you for dinner,and,Milo,thank you for the invitation.
感谢晚餐款待 还有麦洛 感谢你的邀请
I'm sorry the night ended up being so toxic.
很抱歉 今晚搞的这么不开心
I just want you both to know.
我只是想让你们俩知道
Oh,my God!
天啊
I'm sending you the light.
我是给你们带来阳光的
Good night,Lance.
晚安 兰斯
Good night,Judy. I'll walk you out.
晚安朱迪 我送你出去
Well,at least she's sending us the light.
好吧 至少她是给我们送来阳光的
- Are those shoes? - Yeah,kinda. They're a hybrid.
- 这是鞋子吗 - 算是吧 混血
Hybrid of...
混…
Of,you know,just shoes and a foot.
混的是脚和鞋
The human foot.
人脚
You know,some people use a knife and fork for those things.
你知道吗 有人会用刀和叉吃东西的
Yeah? Well,I'm not most people,
是吗 可是我不是大多数人呢
babe,and I think that's why you love me.
宝贝 我想这也是你爱我的原因
'Cause I set myself aside from the pack.
因为我把自己从这些人中独立出来了
- Yeah. - I'll see you tonight,okay?
- 是的 - 晚上见好吗
I gotta get going-
我要走了
- Oh,there he is. - Hey.
- 哦 他来了 - 嘿
What's up,chief?
还好吗 老大
Nothing.
没什么
Okay,I'll check you two dudes later.
好的 我回头再来看你俩
Wallet,Lance. Where is it,baby? Where is it?
钱包呢 兰斯 钱包在哪儿呢？
Is he ever not like that?
他有正常过吗
You know I'm happy that you're here,right?
你知道你能来这里我很高兴 对吧
- Here it comes. - And you can stay as long as you need.
- 又来了 - 你想待多久都可以
- But... - What do you think?
- 但是… - 你觉得呢
- I thought she'd be different. -It doesn't matter.
- 我还以为她会变了呢 - 无关紧要的
You had no right bringing her into this house without asking me.
你没有权利不经过我的同意 就带她进来
Yes,Warden.
是的 狱长
Did you really think she'd be different,
你真的觉得她会不一样了吗
that she'd actually give a shit about us?
你以为她会真的关心我们吗
- Maybe. - Please.
- 也许吧 - 拜托
She's been done with us ever since Dad...
自从父亲过世后 她就跟我们没关系了
I don't even blame him.
我甚至都没怪罪过她
Imagine being married to her. I'd probablyjump off a bridge,too.
想象一下如果娶了她 我也许也会从桥上跳下去
Okay.
好吧
I don't want this. Eat it.
我不想吃了 你吃吧
Okay.
好的
- So,how you feel? - I'm good.
- 那么 你感觉如何 - 我很好
- Yeah? - Yeah.
- 是吗？- 是的
I'm a little embarrassed about the other day.
那天真的有些尴尬
I was on planet Jupiter or something.
我肯定是开小差什么的了
Don't worry about it.
别担心
- I'm a Goof. -No.
- 我是笨蛋 - 不
You're one of my favorites.
你是我最喜欢的学生了
Someone told me to read this once.
有人告诉我读这个
Where to,boss?
去哪儿 老大
- I need you to tell me why you're here. - I'm...
- 我需要你告诉我你为什么来这里 - 我
I just want to make conversation. I just want to see how you're doing.
我只是想找人聊天 我只是想看你到底在干什么
- Really? - Yeah,nothing more.
- 真的吗 - 嗯 没别的
I'm not gonna chop your balls off just yet.
我不会把你蛋蛋剪掉的
Okay,'cause I really wasn't expecting to see you anytime soon.
好吧 我是真的没想到 这么快能又见到你
- I'm sure. - This is weird.
- 那肯定 - 这太奇怪了
I know. I know it's weird.
我知道 这很奇怪
So,how are... What are you... How are you?
那你… 你还好吗
I'm good. Yeah,I'm good. I have a girlfriend.
我很好 嗯 我有女朋友了
Melinda. She's great. She's an optometrist.
梅林达 她很好她是个验光师
Oh,cool.
噢 很好
Really good for me. She gets along with Eric really well.
对我真的很好 她和埃里克也相处非常好
- Eric? - My son.
- 埃里克？- 我儿子
Right,your son.
对 你儿子
Are you living here now?
那你住在这里了吗
No,no,I...
不 我…
Temporarily. I'm just here for... I live in L.A.
暂时的我在这里… 我其实住洛杉矶
- L.A.,that's cool. - Yeah,yeah.
- 洛杉矶很好 - 是的…
- How's that? - Good,good. It's going really well.
- 还可以吧 - 很好 都很好
I mean,the key is just staying busy,you know?
我是说关键是保持一种忙的状态
I've just been acting and auditioning and I just got this agent.
我不停的演试音 然后还找到了经纪人
- Really? - Yeah,I have an agent now.
- 真的吗 - 嗯 我有经纪人了
- An agent. Wow,that's impressive. - Yeah.
- 经纪人 哇哦 真是厉害 - 嗯
What brings you to town other than scaring the shit out of me at a bookstore?
那你不去书店里吓我 跑到城里来干什么
Yeah,that was my sole purpose.
嗯 那是我的唯一目的
No,I... There's a writer's retreat.
不 我… 有个作家的疗养会
You know,I'm writing this one-man show.
我在写一个独角戏
Well,it doesn't surprise me at all. You were always a great writer.
那 这一点完全没有让我感到惊讶 你一直都是个很棒的作家
Oh,well,I had a...
噢 是的 我…
I had a good teacher.
我有个好老师
It's a little cove off the Pawai Bay on the Kona Coast,off the Big Island.
就是大岛屿科娜海岸上 伯瓦伊的一个小港湾
My mate Mike has been there since '05
我朋友迈克 05年就过去了
taking small groups diving,and I'm telling you...
带了一小拨人潜水 我告诉你…
- Pretty? - It's stunning.
- 很美丽吧 - 太美丽了
Sea turtles,manta rays,blue sharks.
海龟 蝠鲼 大青鲨
That sounds incredible.
听起来真不可思议
Except for the sharks,I guess.
除了鲨鱼吧
They're harmless.
它们不伤人的
Besides,
再说了
you could handle a little old shark.
你可以摆平一个老鲨鱼的
- You want another? - Yeah.
- 还想喝吗 - 嗯
No. No.
不 不了
I think I've filled my quota.
我想我已经有点微醉了
I should go.
我该走了
- I haven't finished my drink yet. - Here,I'll take that.
- 我还没喝完呢 - 来 我喝了
Okay,there we go.
好的 我们走吧
That was fun.
很有趣
We had drinks. That was nice. Thank you.
我们喝了酒 很好 谢谢你
I will see you in class.
上课的时候见
Shit.
该死
Sweetie?
亲爱的
Yeah?
什么事
Are we out of pizza pockets?
我们披萨袋是不是没有了
- I think so. - Well,can you put them on the list,please?
- 应该是的 - 那你能不能加到购物清单里
Honey?
亲爱的
So,you'll pick me up after work?
你下班了能来接我吗
Okay.
好的
- All right,well,have a good day at work. - I will.
- 好的 工作顺利 - 好的
- Tell Lance I say hi. - I will.
- 替我跟兰斯打个招呼 - 好的
Okay. All right.
好 走了
- Bye,have a good day. - See ya,bye.
- 再见 愉快 - 拜拜
Bye.
拜
What's up?
怎么了
Do you think I should have a baby?
你觉得我应该要孩子吗
I mean,do you think I would be a good mom?
我是说 你觉得我是个好母亲吗
I don't know.
我不知道
I mean,I think you'd be very attentive.
我是说我觉得你很小心
- Okay. - And maybe a bit overprotective.
- 好吧 - 也许还有点过度保护
Uptight.
紧张
Gee,thanks.
天啊 谢谢
No,I'm just being honest,I'm...
不 我只是诚实的说我
It's a loaded question. I'm sorry.
这个问题很复杂抱歉
I think I'd be an excellent mom.
我觉得我会是个很棒的母亲的
Okay.
好的
What do you want me to say?
那你想让我说啥
How about something that doesn't make me feel like a piece of shit?
要不说一些 不会让我觉得自己一无是处的东西
You know,you're so goddamn selfish,Milo,it's mind-blowing.
你真是自私 麦洛 真让人失望
Maggie.
马吉
Oh,that's classic Maggie,man. Classic.
哦 马吉就是这样的
Yeah,shejustjumped down my throat.
是啊 她真是搞的我没话说
- It was crazy. - Land mines,man.
- 真疯狂 - 到处是地雷
It's like sometimes she and I will be strolling through the park
就好像上一秒 我俩还在公园里笑嘻嘻
laughing,getting along perfect,and then,kaboom,you know?
接着下一秒她就发飙了
A freakin' land mine blows my nuts off.
到处是雷 我都已经习惯了
- You know? - Yeah.
- 你知道吗 - 嗯
And I'll think,
然后我就会想
"Oh,I could've sworn my nuts were there a minute ago.
"哦我可以发誓我前一秒还有想法的"
"I wonder where they went."
"我就奇怪想法上哪儿去了"
- No nuts. - Oh,there they are.
- 没想法 - 噢 本来是有的
They got blown clear across the room.
不过已经被炸开了
They're sliding down that wall over there. My nuts.
都喷到那边墙上去了
And then,you know,when I think about it,
你知道吗 后来我想想
it was probably my fault in the first place,so I'll just apologize to her.
也许一开始就是我的错 所以我就跟她道歉
I probably said something stupid or insensitive,
我看你说了一些很愚蠢的 或者麻木不仁的事
so I'll just tell her that I was sorry,and then it's fine.
所以我就跟她说对不起 然后就没事了
Land mines,dude.
地雷啊 伙计
There she is.
她来了
Your chariot awaits.
你的座驾已经到了
All right,look,I'm sorry.
好的 听着 很对不起
I'm an idiot.
我是白痴
So what else is new?
这有什么
You'd make an amazing mother,okay?
你绝对是个很棒的母亲 好吗
I thought I was too uptight.
我觉得我是太紧张了
I just said that so I didn't have to talk about the real issue,
我那样说是为了 避免谈论
which is your morbid obesity.
真正的问题 也就是你的病态肥胖
I'm surprised you can even leave the house.
我很惊讶你居然能从房子里出来
When was the last time you had your teeth cleaned?
你上次刷牙时什么时候了
- No. No,no,no,no,no. - Come on.
- 不 不 不 - 说啊
- No. - Hey,I am a licensed dental hygienist.
- 不 - 嘿 我是个合格的牙科保健员
Don't you want to see me work?
你不想看我工作吗
No.
不
There are so many planets,yet so little time.
很多行星 时间却很少
All right,okay,I'm gonna take this.
好的 可以了 我要拿走这个了
- Wait,what are you doing? - Milo,that's enough.
- 等下 你干什么 - 麦洛 别闹了
- Wait,wait,wait. I'm not done yet. - Come on,seriously,let go.
- 等下 等下 我还没完呢 - 说真的 放手啦
Let go.
放开
- I'm not done. - Stop.
- 我还没完呢 - 停下来
- Okay,okay,are you ready? - I'm sorry. Okay.
- 好 你准备好了吗 - 抱歉 可以了
'Cause this is serious stuff here.
因为问题很严重
A few more seconds.
再多几秒钟
Give that to me! Give it to me.
把那个给我 给我
Spit. Spit in there.
吐 吐 那边
- Sorry,I think this is broken. - Oh,my...
- 抱歉 我以为这个坏了 - 噢 天啊
Milo,stop.
麦洛 住手
- That thing,you gotta have that thing fixed. - My God!
- 那个东西你得把它修好 - 天啊
You know what? You need to take the edge off.
你得放松下下来
Yeah,right. No.
是 但不要
Everybody's doing it. If you don't do it,no one will ever talk to you.
大家都有这样如果你不放松 也没有人会要你放松
I'm not doing it.
我不要啦
Ross is doing it,Tina's doing it,
罗丝有试过蒂娜有试过
Emily's doing it,Casey's doing it.
埃米莉有试过 凯西有试过
- Shannon is doing it. - Shannon cannot be doing it.
- 莎伦有试过 - 莎伦不会的
- Eric T. and Eric S. - Eric T. and Eric S.,too?
- 埃里克T 还有埃里克S - 埃里克T 和埃里克S 都有试过？
Eric S. and Eric T. are both doing it.
埃里克S 和埃里克T 都有试过
I'm not doing it.
我不要试
I have a very serious question for you.
我有个很认真的问题要问你
Will you go to prom with me?
你会跟我一起去化妆舞会吗
I think you're gassy.
你是不是呛着气了
It's okay,this won't hurt. Ready?
没事的 不会痛的 准备好了吗
- That hurt? - Your elbow went into my arm muscle.
- 疼吗 - 你手肘撞着我的手臂上的肉了
"Your elbow went into my arm muscle,mister."
"你手肘撞着我的手臂上的肉了 先生"
"Your elbow went into my arm muscle,mister.
"Oh,my paper route's gonna be screwed."
"噢 我论文要完蛋了"
I'm getting out of here.
我要走了
- That was a good joke. - Thanks.
- 是个好笑话 - 谢谢
- I have to tell you something,Maggie. - What?
- 我有事情要告诉你 马吉 - 什么
Last month in L.A...
上个月在洛杉矶
What? What?
什么 什么
I ate pussy.
我上了个女的
What?
什么
- What? - I know,I'm not proud of it.
- 什么 - 我知道我不引以为自豪
Why? HOW? Why? Who?
为什么 怎么了 是谁啊
She looked like a young Debbie Harry.
她看起来 就像年轻版的狄波拉·哈利
I was drunk and curious. I just couldn't resist.
我喝醉了 很好奇 我抵抗不了
Oh,my gosh.
噢 天啊
Well,what... How... Verdict?
那什么… 结论是？
I was a little out to sea. I'll tell you that.
我有点尝试过度了 我跟你说
Out in a wet,stormy,
就像在暴风 湿润
pungent sea.
艰辛的大海里一样
- All right,now your turn. - My turn?
- 好了 轮到你了 - 我？
I told you a secret. You have to tell me a secret.
我告诉你了一个秘密 你也应该告诉我一个
- I don't have any secrets. - Maggie.
- 我没有秘密 - 马吉
Maggie Dean.
马吉·迪恩
I'm on birth control.
我在避孕
Really?
真的吗
Yeah.
是的
I hide it in a basket in the bathroom.
我藏在卫生间的篮子里了
I figure Lance won't be looking for butterfly decorative soaps anytime soon.
我想兰斯应该不会那么快 用到蝴蝶形状的那个肥皂
So,it's terrible.
很糟糕
Wouldn't it be easierjust to tell Lance
你直接跟兰斯说
you're not ready to have a kid?
你还没准备好要孩子 不是更简单点吗
Yeah.
是的
It would be a lot easier.
那会简单很多
But there's a little more to it than that.
但事情不只是这么简单
What?
什么
- It's really bad. - What?
- 很糟糕的 - 什么
I slept with my scuba instructor.
我跟我的潜水老师睡了
Maggie.
马吉
I know,it sounds like a porno.
我知道这听起来很像黄片
Just once?
就一次？
- With him? -"With him"?
- 跟他？- "跟他"？
Yeah. I took a French cooking class like six months ago.
是的 我6个月前 还上了法国烹饪课程
Maggie!
马吉
And a nature photography course... I met this guy.
还有自然 摄影课程 我认识了这个人
It's a fetish is what it sounds like.
听起来像恋物狂
If Lance finds out,it will destroy him
如果兰斯知道了 他会受不了的
and I will not be able to live with myself.
那我就只有单身一人了
Please say something.
说点什么啊
I guess Lance just doesn't do it for you.
我想兰斯不会那样对你的
But why? He's so great.
为什么 他真的很不错的
He's so sweet and cute and nice and he would make such a great dad,
他很贴心很好 很帅气 他也是个模范爸爸
and he is the polar opposite of all the assholes that I'm used to dating.
他是我见过 最不混蛋的一个家伙了
He doesn't deserve a fucking whore as a wife.
他不该娶到一个 像妓女一样的人当老婆
- You're not a whore. - Oh,really?
- 你不是妓女 - 哦是吗
- So don't say that,please. - What would you call it,then?
- 所以别那样说 - 那你说我是啥
You're a restless housewife with whore-like tendencies.
你是个焦躁不安的少妇 有变成妓女的倾向
Shut up.
闭嘴
It doesn't help.
帮倒忙
Do you love him?
你爱他吗
Yeah,I do. He's...
是的 当然了
He's good.
他很棒的
Maybe good isn't your thing.
也许你喜欢的不是"很棒"
Maybe.
也许
What am I gonna do?
那我应该怎么办
You're gonna do a bunch of nitrous with your gay brother?
要跟你的同性恋弟弟好好聊聊吗
You wanna talk about this more downstairs?
要不要更"深入"的聊一下
Sure.
当然
- Oh,this hurts my back. - Me,too,my spine.
- 噢 背都疼了 - 我也是
- Why did I say,"Let's talk downstairs"? - I don't know.
- 为什么我要说"深入" - 我不知道
- Wait,what time is it? - I don't know.
- 等下现在几点了 - 我不知道
Shit.
该死
- What? - Come on,we gotta go.
- 什么 - 来我们得走了
- Why? - I have a meeting.
- 为什么 - 我还有约
You have a meeting? With who?
你有约？跟谁昵
With Kevin Clancy from high school.
凯文·克兰西高中的那个
- Really? - Yeah.
- 真的吗 - 是的
Cool. Can I come?
很好 我能去吗
No. I think he wanted to make it kind of like a one-on-one kind of meeting.
不行吧 我觉得 他想跟我单独见面什么的
- Is that weird? I'm sorry. - No.
- 很奇怪吧 抱歉 - 不
- No,it's fine. - Is that cool?
- 没事的 - 没事吧？
- Yeah,yeah,yeah. - All right,we gotta go,though.
- 当然了 - 好的 那我们得走了
We gotta go.
我们得走了
Oh,my God! You're killing me.
哦 天啊 你简直是杀了我
No,no,no,but,listen,it's like,"Melville,dude,please,
不 不 不 听着就像"梅尔维尔老兄 拜托"
"just write me a story about a whale,a guy who catches a whale.
"跟我写一个白鲸的故事吧一个抓鲸鱼的伙计"
"Why does it have to be 800 pages of the history of whaling
"那为什么非得用800页来说捕鲸历史呢"
"and all this existential crisis bullshit?"
"还有什么灭绝危及什么的"
Like,who gives a shit
谁会在意这些东西
when the writing is that weird and funny and rich and alive
如果写作的时候是那么奇怪 那么有趣那么丰富生动呢
and did I mention weird?
而且我有说过奇怪吗
You know what I mean,though? But with class.
你知道我什么意思吗 那么优秀的作品
And pretentious. And pretentious.
自命不凡还有狂妄
There's a great Moby Dick illustrated that I think you'd love.
《白鲸记》里就有说过 我觉得你会喜欢
- There's a pop-up whale at the end. - Fuck you.
- 结尾是个竖起来的鲸鱼 - 去你的
Didn't I give you a whale?
我是不是给你了个鲸鱼
I feel like I gave you,like,
我感觉我好像给你了一个
a copper figurine for your birthday that I got at that...
铜币小雕像作为你的生日礼物
Wow! You carry that with you?
哇哦 你还带着的？
I don't know. It's,like,a little good luck charm or something.
我不知道 有点像是幸运吉祥物吧
Well,it's working.
很有效
- Is it? I don't know if it is. - Yeah.
- 是吗 我不知道是不是 - 当然了
Yeah,Mr. Fancy L.A. Agent.
是啊 洛杉矶经纪人先生
I should've kept that whale for myself.
我应该把那鲸鱼留给我自己
It's not that big of a deal. He's not that big of an agent.
也没什么的了 他又不是什么大经纪人
I think it's incredible.
我觉得很难以置信
I always knew you'd do something amazing with your life.
我一直都知道你会做一些 让你人生不同的事情
I'm proud of you,Milo.
麦洛 我为你感到自豪
Do you wanna get out of here?
你出去吗
Those lobster cages can knock you right off.
这些龙虾的笼子 可以把你敲晕
What?
什么
Well,actually,they're called lobster pots,
实际上 他们叫这个是"诱捕龙虾的笼子"
but they can knock these guys right off the deck.
它们可以把这些家伙在甲板上敲晕
They're real dangerous.
它们很危险的
I think those are crabs.
这些应该是蟹吧
- Where? - Everywhere.
- 哪里 - 到处都是
Oh,yeah,maybe they are.
噢 是 也许是的
No,they are.
不 他们就是
So,how's Milo working out?
那么 麦洛工作如何了
Good. He's definitely doing his best,but he's been... He's trying.
很好 他绝对是尽力了 但是他 很努力
Good.
很好
I love you.
我爱你
I love you,too.
我也爱你
I really love you.
我真的爱你
Thank you.
谢谢
God,I can't believe he's 16.
天啊 我不敢相信他16了
It's strange,man. Having a kid that old.
很奇怪吧 有这么大的孩子了
He just got his license.
他刚考了驾照
I'm like,"Really?
我想说"真的吗"
"I'm old enough to have a kid who can drive?"
"我有个孩子已经年长到可以开车了？"
My God!
不敢相信
Does he know about me and you?
他知道你和我吗
No,no,God,no.
不 当然不知道
He knows I used to teach
他知道我以前是教书的
and sometimes he asks why I stopped,you know,but...
有时候他会问为什么我不教了 但是…
What do you tell him?
那你告诉他什么了
That it wasn't my thing.
跟他说这不是我喜欢的
- I'm sorry,Rich. - No,Milo,you don't ever have to apologize.
- 抱歉 里奇 - 不 麦洛 你不必道歉
You didn't do anything wrong. You understand me?
你没做错什么 你明白吗
Okay.
好的
Look,I know what happened was weird and illegal and shit,
听着 我知道之前发生的事情很奇葩 而且也不合法
but it really meant something to me.
但是对我来说 真的意味着很多
And we're adults.
我们都是成年人了
Well,I'm an adult.
我是成年人
God,I feel like the freshman asking the senior to the dance.
天啊 我感觉像是大一的学生 邀请大四的去跳舞
That's part of the problem. There's...
这就是问题所在…
There's a freshman/senior dynamic between us.
我们之间有几届的隔阂
There doesn't have to be.
不必如此的
Milo,get up. Lance is leaving in 10 minutes.
麦洛 起来了 兰斯10分钟后就走了
Milo?
麦洛
Milo,is that your phone?
麦洛 那是你的手机吗
Oh,shit,what time is it?
噢 糟糕 几点了
It's after 9:00.
已经9点过了
Fuck,I'm late for work.
该死 我要迟到了
You and me both.
我俩都是
So,here.
这个 给你
- "Sunrise in Manhattan." -it's a romantic comedy.
- "曼哈顿日出" - 是个浪漫喜剧
- About what,Balzac and Foucault? -No,it's actually pretty straightforward.
- 说什么的巴尔扎克和傅科？不其实故事很简单
I wrote it for,you know,like,Jennifer Aniston or Kate Hudson.
我是写给 詹妮弗·安妮斯顿或者凯特·哈德森的
And I don't want to be presumptuous,
我不想冒昧
but I thought,you know,if you wanted to read it
但是我想如果你想读的话
and maybe if you liked it,you could pass it along to your agent?
如果你喜欢的话 你可以给你的经纪人看看
Yeah,okay. Yeah,totally.
嗯 当然 可以
- Yeah,I could totally... - Cool.
- 嗯 我会的… - 很好
...pass it on if... I'll read it.
会给的… 我会读的
- Cool. - Yeah.
- 很好 - 嗯
I kind of... I need you to leave.
我…我该走了
Okay. Yeah,sure.
好的 当然了
- Last night was fun. - Yeah.
- 昨晚很开心 - 嗯
Kind of a blast from the past.
就像是过去回忆的唤醒
Yeah,make sure the door locks when you close it.
是的 锁门的时候锁好
Greetings,Ms. Dean.
早上好 迪恩小姐
What brings you around these parts?
你怎么来这里了
It was a mistake.
那是个错
All right.
好吧
I mean it,the whole thing.
我是认真的 整个事都错了
Fine.
好吧
Is that all?
仅此而已？
Yeah. Yeah,that's all.
是的 是的 没错
What are you doing?
你干什么呢
No,Billy,I'm serious.
不 比利 我是认真的
No.
不
Bullshit! Bullshit! Bullshit! Bullshit.
混蛋 混蛋 混蛋 混蛋 混蛋
Bullshit.
该死的
Bull shit.
该死
Hello.
你好呀
Where were you this morning?
你今天早上去哪儿了
Well,Kevin had a friend,and last night,I got lucky.
凯文有个朋友 昨晚我幸运了一把
Well,you missed work,so,not cool.
可是 你错过工作了 所以不怎么样
I was a little late. Lance understood.
我只是迟到了一点 兰斯能理解的
You have to get your shit together,Milo.
麦洛 你自己的事情得控制好点
That is a very interesting statement coming from you.
这句话从你嘴里说出来真有意思
- You know what? - What?
- 你知道吗 - 什么
Wow.
哇哦
What are you doing?
你干什么
Milo.
麦洛
望著你的双眼 我看见了天堂
∮ Looking in your eyes I see a paradise ∮
我发现的这个世界完美得不像真的
∮ This world that I found is too good to be true ∮
伫立在你身旁 我想给你许许多多
∮ Standing here beside you,want so much to give you ∮
给你我心中的爱 和我对你的感受
∮ This love in my heart that I'm feeling for you ∮
就让别人说我们疯了
∮ Let 'em say we're crazy ∮
我一点都不在乎
∮ I don't care about that ∮
把手放在我的手心 宝贝
∮ Put your hand in my hand,baby ∮
不要回头
∮ Don't ever look back ∮
让周遭的世界摔成碎片
∮ Let the world around us just fall apart ∮
宝贝 只要我俩心相连 一定可以成功
∮ Baby,we can make it if we're heart to heart ∮
我俩可以一齐筑梦
∮ And we can build this dream together ∮
永远昂首挺立
∮ Standing strong forever ∮
什麼都阻挡不了我们
∮ Nothing's gonna stop us now ∮
如果这世界不再有恋人
∮ And if this world runs out of lovers ∮
我俩依然拥有彼此
∮ We'll still have each other ∮
此刻 什麼都无法阻挡我们
∮ Nothing's gonna stop us ∮
什麼都无法阻挡我们
∮ Nothing's gonna stop us now ∮
Okay,I got it.
好了我知道了
我很高兴我找到了你
∮ I'm so glad I found you ∮
我会守在你身旁
∮ I'm not gonna lose you ∮
无论如何 我都不要失去你
∮ Whatever it takes,I will stay here with you ∮
度过美好时光 熬过艰难岁月
∮ Take it to the good times,see it through the bad times ∮
无论如何 我都会这麼做
∮ Whatever it takes is what I'm gonna do ∮
就让别人说我们疯了
∮ Let 'em say we're crazy ∮
他们知道些什麼？
∮ What do they know? ∮
宝贝 把你的手臂紧抱著我 千万不要放手
∮ Put your arms around me,baby,don't ever let go ∮
让周遭的世界摔成碎片
∮ Let the world around us just fall apart ∮
宝贝 只要我俩心相连 一定可以成功
∮ Baby,we can make it if we're heart to heart ∮
我俩可以一齐筑梦
∮ And we can build this dream together ∮
永远昂首挺立
∮ Standing strong forever ∮
什麼都阻挡不了我们
∮ Nothing's gonna stop us now ∮
如果这世界不再有恋人
∮ And if this world runs out of lovers ∮
我俩依然拥有彼此
∮ We'll still have each other ∮
此刻 什麼都无法阻挡我们
∮ Nothing's gonna stop us,nothing's gonna stop us ∮
我所需要的就只有你
∮ Ooh,all that I need is you ∮
你就是我的一切
∮ All that I ever need ∮
我只想
∮ All that I want to do ∮
永远的抱著你
∮ Is hold you forever ∮
永永远远
∮ Ever and ever ∮
我俩可以一齐筑梦
∮ And we can build this dream together ∮
永远昂首挺立
∮ Standing strong forever... ∮
Hi.
嗨
Is your dad home?
你爸爸在家吗？
Yeah,hold on.
在 等一下
Dad,some guy's at the door for you.
爸爸 有个家伙找你
I'm sorry,I thought you had him...
对不起 我以为你让他…
What are you doing? You can't be here.
你干什么？你不能来这里
That's my kid in there.
我的孩子在这儿
Okay,I thought you only had him on the weekends.
好吧 我以为你只是周末跟他一起
I have a life,Milo. A whole life.
我有我的生活 麦洛 完整的生活
Give me a shot of Cuervo,please.
麻烦给我一杯龙舌兰
Can I have another one,please?
再来一杯可以吗
Hey.
嘿
What are you doing up here?
你在这里做什么？
I'm waiting for you,Mr. Big Officer Man.
我在等你 大警官先生
The fuck you say?
你说什么呢？
Thank you. Thank you very much.
谢谢 非常感谢
No problem. Take care,now.
不用谢 保重
Thanks.
谢谢
Maggie,don't freak out.
马吉 别紧张
What is going on?
怎么回事
You wouldn't understand.
你不懂的
Try me. You might be surprised.
说出来听听 也许我能理解的
I get depressed about my life and I do stupid things. That's it.
我因为我的人生 和我所做的傻事而沮丧 就这些
We all get sad about our lives,Milo.
我们对自己的人生都很伤心 麦洛
That doesn't mean we go jumping off of rooftops.
那也不意味着要去跳楼
I wasn't gonna jump.
我没想跳楼
Okay,well,how do I know that?
那我怎么会知道
Okay,I'm sorry.
对不起
I can't take this,Milo. I can't right now. I can't.
我真搞不明白 麦洛 我现在就很不明白
Hey,I'm sorry.
嘿 对不起
Do you remember Justin Meyer in eighth grade?
你还记得8年级的贾斯廷·梅耶尔吗？
Jock,asshole,he used to fuck with me all the time?
那时经常跟我在一起的那个运动员
Dad,he told me... He said,"Guys like Justin,
爸爸告诉我说"像贾斯廷那种男生
"like,high school is the best it's ever gonna get for them.
"高中时代是他们最好的时候"
"They're gonna peak in high school,
"高中是他们的巅峰期"
"and the rest of their life is just gonna be a disappointment."
"然而接下来的人生只会不尽人意"
And that kids like me,
而像我这样的孩子
that I would soar after high school.
高中后会突飞猛进
And,in fact,I would sit there,
事实上未来的10年里
I would fast-forward 10 years into the future
我会进展的很迅速
and I would think about our high school reunion
然后我会想到高中同学会
and seeing Justin,and he would just be this fat,balding guy
见到贾斯廷 他只是个肥胖秃顶的家伙
who,you know,is the assistant manager at some sporting goods store,
就是一个 体育用品商店的副经理
and I would be this famous actor
而我成了一个著名的演员
who lives in L.A. or New York and I have this beautiful boyfriend.
住在洛杉矶或者纽约 还有漂亮的男朋友
And I'm happy-
而且我很幸福
Do you know I looked Justin up online?
你知道我在网上查到贾斯廷了吗？
And do you know what he's doing now?
你知道他在做什么吗？
He's an electrician,
他是个电工
and he has two beautiful daughters and a pretty wife.
而且还有两个漂亮的女儿 和一个漂亮的老婆
And he's happy...
他很幸福
And it turns out that...
原来…
ltjust turns out that I'm the one that peaked in high school.
原来我才是 那个高中是巅峰时期的人
You know,if that's not depressing,then...
如果这还不令人沮丧那么…
So,that's it,sweetie?
那就到此为止吧 亲爱的
You're not a famous actor?
你不是个名演员？
'Cause I got news for you. No one's a famous actor.
因为我告诉你 没有一个人是名演员
George Clooney's a famous actor.
乔治·克鲁尼是个名演员
Okay,George Clooney,I guess that's one exception.
好吧 乔治·克鲁尼 我猜那是个例外
But the rest of us are just walking around
但是我们其他人都只是在徘徊
trying not to be disappointed
努力生活的
with the way that our lives turned out.
没那么不尽人意
And either we find a way to deal or...
无论是寻找解决的方法 还是…
I need to know you're not gonna check out on me.
你要知道 你不能离开我
I'll do my best.
我尽量
What?
什么啊？
What are you doing?
你在做什么？
It's gotta be in here somewhere.
应该在这里的
Oh,my God!
我的天啊
Wow!
哇
Oh,here it is! I found it!
噢 在这里我找到了
Oh,my God! You still have that thing?
天啊 你还留着这个？
- We're going out. - What?
- 我们出去吧 - 什么？
It is Halloween,Lance is at fantasy football,
今天是万圣节 兰斯在玩梦幻足球
I say you put on something pretty and/or freaky.
我觉得你穿件好看的 或者恐怖的衣服
Preferably both.
最好又好看又恐怖
Yeah.
好
I can do this better myself.
我自己化得还更好
No,I wanna do it.
不行 我想帮你化
Okay.
好了
Tell me if you don't like it.
要告诉我你喜不喜欢
I will tell you immediately if I don't like it.
要是不喜欢的话 我会马上告诉你的
Is that a good scream?
这是好看的意思吗？
That was a great scream. I love it.
是好极了的意思 我喜欢
Oh,my God! I can't believe it still fits.
天啊 我真不敢相信居然还能穿
- I know. - Look at me.
- 我知道 - 你看我
You have better legs than I do,by the way.
你的腿比我的还好看
I have a body like a frog.
我的身材就像只青蛙
- No,you don't. - Yes,I do.
- 没有一点也不会 - 真的
What does that mean?
什么意思？
Just a big belly and long arms and long legs.
就是大肚子长手长腿的样子
Justhkeu.
就像…
Oh,Michelle Waller.
米歇尔·沃勒
Pregnant again,baby number three.
她又怀孕了生第3个宝宝
- Baby number three? - Yeah.
- 第3个宝宝？- 对
- Shit,I didn't even know she was married. - Yeah.
- 我都还不知道她结婚了 - 是啊
We haven't done the cemetery walk since Dad died.
自从爸爸去世后 我们就没有来墓地散过步了
I know.
是啊
Oh,my God,watch your step.
天啊 小心你的脚下
God,it has not changed a bit.
天啊 一点都没有变
I had my first wine cooler here.
我第一次喝清爽酒 就是在这喝的
- With who? - Jenny Copeland.
- 跟谁啊？- 珍妮·科普兰
- That makes sense. - Yeah.
- 那可以理解 - 是啊
Oh,wow!
哇
Dad loved Halloween.
爸爸喜欢万圣节
Who can blame him?
这也难怪
Scram.
走开
Get outta here.
快走开
What,are you deaf?
你是聋子吗
I'm not deaf. It's Halloween,assholes.
我不是聋子 今天是万圣节 混蛋
Fucking people.
该死的
Oh,my God!
我的天啊
Wait,what was the name of the...
那个叫什么…
...adolescent psychiatrist that they assigned us?
青少年精神病专家分配给我的？
- What was her name? - Oh,shit.
- 她叫什么名 - 该死
- Mary? - Mamie Mortimer.
- 玛丽？- 玛米·莫蒂默
- Mamie Mortimer. - Mamie Mortimer and her fucking journals.
- 玛米·莫蒂默 - 玛米·莫蒂默和她该死的日记
Giant sweaters.
穿着巨大的毛衣
What was with those sweaters?
为什么要穿大毛衣
Huge! She's not a big woman.
她有不是很肥大
Every day was Christmas for Mamie Mortimer.
对玛米·莫蒂默来说每天都是圣诞节
Oh,my God! "Did you write that in yourjournal?"
我的天啊 "你把那记在日记了吗？"
"There's nothing that can't be solved byjournaling."
"没有什么不能用日记来解决的"
"Oh,your dad died? Put it in a journal.
"噢 你爸爸去世了？记在日记里吧"
- "You forgot about it,didn't ya?" - "My dad died,I feel better."
- "你忘记了吧？" - "我爸爸去世了我感觉好点了"
She had a tough gig,though.
她管得很严
I mean,we were not good kids.
我们不是好孩子
I mean,what do you do to two kids whose dad...
对于两个失去爸爸的孩子 你会怎么做…
- You make them keep a journal. -Yeah,I mean,we were 14.
- 会让他们记日记 - 对 我们那时14岁
God,we were ungrateful bastards,though. Right?
天啊 我们是忘恩负义的混蛋 是吗？
Speak for yourself.
你说你自己吧
I was an angel. I don't know what you're talking about.
我可是个天使 我不知道你在说什么
Maggie.
马吉
- "Maggie." - Maggie.
- "马吉" - 马吉
Let me... Oh,wait. Let me see it.
让我… 等下 让我看看
What?
什么？
I want to see it.
我想看看
Oh,what is that,a new place?
那是什么换地方了吗？
No,it's always been here.
没有 一直都在这里
Oh,there she is,dancing away.
我看到了她在跳舞
Of course she is.
那当然
Did you think I got rid of it?
你以为我把她消掉了吗？
I don't know. You're a tricky bird,Magpie.
我不知道 你是个难以捉摸的鸟 喜鹊
How'd we go 10 years without talking?
要是我们10年不说话 那会怎么样？
Oh,it's probably not worth talking about now.
那也许现在就不会坐一起讲话了
Probably not.
有可能
Let me take my hat off.
我把帽子脱掉
- Come on. - Be polite.
- 拜托 - 这样礼貌点
Magpie.
喜鹊
Oh,peeing in a dress at a urinal is actually not that hard.
穿着裙子在小便池尿尿 其实也没那么难
I'm gonna go.
我要走了
Do you want another round?
你不再喝一点吗？
I'm gonna go.
我要走了
Hey,hey.
嘿 嘿
Wait up,Maggie.
等下 马吉
Hey,what's going on?
嘿 怎么回事？
Kevin Clancy?
凯文·克兰西？
Kevin Clancy moved to Miami six years ago.
6年前凯文·克兰西搬去迈阿密了
He was in town for the weekend.
他周末都还在城里的
What? What is this?
什么？怎么了
I saw your cell phone.
我看到你的手机了
You have a missed call from Rich Levitt.
你有一个里奇·莱维特的未接来电
Are you sleeping with him?
你是不是跟他上床了？
Some of us have our secrets and some of us have our reasons,Maggie.
我们有秘密 都是有自己的原因的 马吉
Wow.
哇
So,what,you're still attracted to child molesters?
这么说 你还是喜欢恋童癖？
Is that it?
是吗？
He's not a child molester.
他不是个恋童癖
You were 15 and he was your English teacher.
你那时才15岁 他是你的英语老师
You didn't see the way he treated me.
你不知道他是怎么教我的
- He wanted to fuck you. - Who are you to judge,okay?
- 他想跟你上床 - 你不要乱作判断
You've had boyfriends since you were in the fifth grade,okay?
你在5年级的时候就有男朋友了 好吗？
I was 15. I had never been kissed before.
我那时已经15岁了 还从来没有接过吻
- So what if he was my teacher? - So what?
- 就算他是我老师那又怎么样？- 怎么样？
He made me feel good! He made me feel good about myself!
他让我感觉很好 让我感觉自己特别好
I don't want to hear how he made you feel.+
我不想听他给你什么感觉
You know what? You wanna go hang out with Rich Levitt,
你知道吗？你要是想跟里奇·莱维特在一起
go ahead. I am not gonna stop you.
随便你我不会阻止你的
But when all that shit went down,
但是等到出问题了
I know,looking back,I was right.
再回过头来 我知道我是对的
And I can't feel guilty about it anymore.
我也不会再觉得惭愧
And it could've been a lot worse.
而且本来就更糟糕
He could've gone to fucking jail,Milo.
他应该坐牢的 麦洛
Do you realize that?
你知道吗？
He is lucky that we dealt with this quietly.
他很幸运 那是因为我们悄悄的解决了这件事
And I know you blame me,and I know you think
我知道你怪我 我也知道你认为
I ruined this blossoming relationship between you and him.
是我毁了你和他的热恋关系
I know you think I ruined his life,that I ruined your life,
我知道你认为我毁了他的一生 我毁了你的一生
but I did what I had to do.
但是这都是我该做的
Look,it had nothing to do with you.
听着 这跟你一点关系都没有
That is bullshit.
胡说
You're my brother.
你是我的弟弟
And we're supposed to be there for each other.
我们应该互相帮助
And if you don't get that by now,then,
要是你现在还没有明白那…
I don't know,I guess I'll talk to you in another 10 years.
我也不知道 我猜要10年后我再跟你讲话
- Maggie,wait. - This sucks.
- 马吉 等等 - 这很恶心
I was having such a good night with you.
今晚过得真是好
Sunday,Monday,Tuesday...
星期天 星期一 星期二
Sunday,Monday...
星期天 星期一…
Oh,shit.
该死
- Morning,chief. - Morning.
- 早上好 头 - 早上好
Well,looks like your sis is down for the count.
你姐姐好像没力起来
I think she's got,like,food poisoning or something.
我想她可能是食物中毒什么的了
Right,or something.
是的 有可能
Maybe we should have a dude's day.
也许我们可以过个男生节
- A what? - You know,dude's day.
- 什么？- 你懂的 男生节
I think your version of dude's day
我想你的男生节
and my version of dude's day are totally different.
和我的男生节完全不一样
Oh,shit.
该死的
Oh,shit!
Come on,man. You almost had it that time.
加油 伙计 你刚刚差点就够着了
Lance,this harness has my balls in my fucking throat.
兰斯 这个安全带勒到我的蛋蛋了
Can I please come down?
我可以下来吗？
It's all part of the experience,buddy boy.
都要经历的小子
The only good thing about this experience is that every guy in here's gorgeous.
这个经历唯一的好处就是 在这的每个男人都很帅
Yeah,it's great here,man.
是的 这里很不错的
You're surrounded by a bunch of hunks. It's beautiful.
你被一群大帅哥围着呢 太好了
Come on,you gotta use the pain. Get inspired by it.
加油 你要利用痛苦 收到激励
What are you,some sort of,like,climbing Nazi?
你是什么啊 攀岩纳粹党的吗？
I just believe in you,that's all.
我只是相信 你仅此而已
Come on,I saw you out there working at the park.
加油 我看过你在公园工作
You got it in you,dude. I believe in you.
你可以的伙计 我相信你加油
- Come on. - You're such a piece of shit,Lance.
- 你真是 - 你就是坨屎 兰斯
Yeah,awesome. Awesome.
对 太棒了 真了不起
Just keep doing it just like that,man.
就是这样坚持住
That's what I'm talking about! Boo-ya,dude!
这就是这个意思太棒了
- To dude's day. - To dude's day.
- 为男生节干杯 - 干杯
I gotta tell you,you were channeling my middle school P.E. teacher out there.
我告诉你 你跟我中学的体育老师有的一拼了
Yeah,you were into it,huh?
是的 你不是挺喜欢的吗
- Yeah,it was very... You're very motivating. - Thank you.
- 是 真的… 你很会激励人 - 谢谢
You're gonna be a good dad someday. That was good.
你以后一定是个好爸爸很好
Thanks,man.
谢谢
It's funny,'cause all my buddies,
有趣的是 我所有的朋友
they're scared shitless about the whole fatherhood thing,
他们都非常害怕当爸爸
and,yeah,I just know that I'm ready for it.
我只知道我已经准备好了
That's why the whole pregnancy thing has been frustrating,you know?
所以怀孕这件事 很令人沮丧你知道吗？
Just wanna make sure I'm not firing blanks,you know?
只想证实一下我生育能力没有问题
Right.
对
Guess I'm just a little paranoid.
我才我只是有点妄想症
Have you noticed her acting a little strange at all lately?
你有没有发现 她最近的行为有点奇怪？
Like,I mean...
比如… 我想说…
I don't know what I mean.
我不知道我想说什么
I know what you mean,yeah.
我知道你的意思
It'll all happen in Hawaii. That's how I feel.
我觉得夏威夷就有可能
Just in between the trade winds and the palm trees
在那种信风棕榈树
and the people and,you know,exotic spices.
还有那里的人 异国的香料
Yeah.
嗯
Maybe we'll do it in a hammock.
或许我们可以在吊床上那个
Hawaii's definitely baby-making country.
夏威夷肯定是个造人的好地方
You know,Maggie can be very secretive.
你知道 马吉是个非常神秘的人
Like,when we were kids and stuff,
在我们小的时候
she would hide cigarettes and things like that around the house.
她喜欢把一些香烟之类的藏在家附近
You know,places you wouldn't think to look.
那些你想不到的地方
Maybe there's some medication or something that's affecting things.
也许是一些药物 或者感人的东西
Just a thought.
只是我的一个想法
Yeah,I don't think Maggie'd hide something like that from me.
嗯 我想马吉不会把东西藏起来 不让我看
- I'm sure you're right. - Yeah.
- 你说的没错 - 嗯
Hey,miss,do you need help with anything?
嘿 小姐有什么可以帮到你的吗？
Yeah,you know what? I'm... I just...
嗯 你知道吗？我 我
I'm a little late.
我的大姨妈有还没来
But not seriously late,just a little.
但又不是很多天晚了只是几天
But I'm... You know what? I don't need this.
但是我… 我还是不需要这个
I'm fine,thanks.
我没事 谢谢
Thank you for putting that back. Thanks.
谢谢你把它放回去 谢谢
What else did I need?
我还要买什么呢？
...puked all over the field.
…吐得到处都是
Maggie Dean?
马吉·迪恩？
It's Carlie Van der Hoff.
我是卡莉·万德霍夫
Garfield High?
加菲尔德高中？
- Yeah,hi. - Yeah,my God! How are you?
- 哦 嗨 - 我的天啊 你好吗？
- I'm fine. - Oh,this is Cullen.
- 我很好 - 噢 这是卡伦
- Say hi,Cullen. - Hi.
- 打个招呼卡伦 - 嗨
He's the oldest of my rug rats.
他是我最大的孩子
Yeah,but look at you.
看看你
Are you visiting family?
你过来探亲吗？
No,no,I live here.
没有 我住在这里
- Really? - Yeah.
- 真的吗？- 是的
That's so weird that we've never run into each other.
真是奇怪 我们从没碰到过
- Yeah. - I'm at the school employees credit union.
- 是啊 - 我在校职工信用社工作
- Mom. - Cullen,hush.
- 妈妈 - 卡伦
If you're bored,go wait in the car.
你要是觉得无聊的话 先去车里等着
- Oh,I'm gonna be leaving. - Beat it.
- 我也要走了 - 快去
- Kiss my ass! - Hey,you watch it,mister!
- 去你的 - 嘿 你小心点
Back at ya!
退给你
What a little shit.
真是个不省心的小混蛋
Can you believe kids today? The attitudes.
你能想象现在孩子们的态度吗？
- Do you have kids? - No.
- 你有孩子吗？- 没有
Well,you're lucky because they are little shits.
那你真是幸运 因为他们都是群小混蛋
So,how are you? How's Milo?
你好吗？麦洛怎么样？
Tell me everything.
跟我聊聊吧
I'm all right.
我挺好的
- You got married? - I did.
- 你结婚了吗 - 结了
Of course,you always had so many boyfriends.
当然 你一直都有很多男朋友
Oh,boy.
天啊
Are you okay?
你没事吧？
Carlie,can you... Can you give me one second?
卡莉 你可以等我一下吗？
- Yeah. - Be right back.
- 可以 - 马上回来
Thank you,thank you. Oh,thank...
谢谢 谢谢 哦 谢谢
It's over.
我们分手吧
No,for real.
不 我说真的
Hi.
嗨
Honey,what's going on here?
亲爱的 这是怎么回事
Those are old.
那都是以前的
Okay,well,the prescription says that they're from last month,so...
处方上写的是 上个月的 所以…
Honey,I'm sorry that...
亲爱的 很抱歉…
Listen...
听着…
If you don't want to have kids right now,
如果你现在不想要孩子
we can talk about that,okay?
你可以跟我们商量好吗？
You don't need to lie to me.
你不用骗我
Sweetie,you're freaking me out right now.
亲爱的 你现在吓到我了
I'm a sick person,Lance.
我有病 兰斯
What do you mean?
什么意思？
I've been with other men since we've been married.
我们结婚以来 我还跟另外几个男人在一起
Three.
一共3个
Three other men.
3个别的男人
I wasn't in love with any of them. I know that doesn't matter.
我没有爱上他们任何一个 我知道那不重要
I'm so sorry.
对不起
I'm sorry.
Lance?
兰斯
Look,he was confused. I felt terrible for him.
听着 他很困惑 我觉得他很难受
- Hey! - You had no right!
- 嘿 - 你没权干涉我们
Things were gonna crash down eventually.
终究会有水落石出的一天
No,you were just trying to get back at me.
不 你只是想报复我
- I was trying to help you. - You just ruined my marriage.
- 我是想帮你 - 你毁了我的婚姻
- What marriage? - Fuck you.
- 什么样的婚姻？- 去你的
Look,you're miserable,
听着你很痛苦
and if you're too chicken shit to do anything about it,then I will.
要是你不敢做什么 我可以帮你做
Oh,so,you know what's best for me?
是吗 那你知道什么对我来说是最好的吗？
Yes,you're my sister. We're supposed to help each other out.
知道 你是我姐姐 我们应诙互相帮助
- You said that. - This is different!
- 你说过的 - 这不一样
- How? - We are adults. This is my marriage.
- 怎么不一样？- 我们都是成年人了 这是我的婚姻
If you think that's a marriage,then you're fucking nuts,okay?
如果你觉得这是婚姻 那你就是个傻子
I'm sorry. Enjoy your marital bliss.
对不起 好好享受你婚姻的幸福吧
Okay,yeah,go. Leave anyway. This is not working out.
好 快走 走的越远越好这没用的
You know what the sad thing is? Is that we're a good team.
你知道最可悲的是什么吗？可悲的是我们是一个好团队
Oh,yeah,and you'd be a real hoot to have around
是的 如果你没有这么混蛋的话
if you weren't such a fuckup.
那跟在一起还是挺好的
We're both fuckups,okay?
我们俩都很混蛋 好吗？
And I'm tired of you acting like you're the healthy one
我受够了好像你才是正常人
and I'm your special needs kid.
而我是个有特殊需要的孩子
What does it even matter anymore,Milo?
这已经不重要了 麦洛
You got your revenge. You got it.
你已经报仇了你成功了
I was trying to lay it out on the table.
我只是想把事实摆出来
That's what I was trying to do.
我想帮你
- You wanna lay it out on the table? - Yes!
- 你想把事实摆出来？- 是的
Okay,then,go for it.
好 那你去啊
- You're emotionally unstable. - You're a prick.
- 你情绪太不稳定了 - 你就是个蠢货
You need professional help.
你需要专业的帮助
And this coming from a guy who just tried to kill himself.
这是一个刚刚还想自杀的人说的
Maybe I should try fucking all my problems away.
也许我应该把自己问题解决好
Well,maybe next time you should cut deeper.
也许下回你应该再割得深一点
Oh,no. No,no,no,no,no,no.
噢 不要千万别死
Shit.
见鬼
Fuck.
该死的
Come on. Fuck.
拜托 该死的
Come on,come on,come on.
拜托 拜托 拜托
There we go. There we go.
快醒醒 快醒醒
Yeah,yeah,yeah. There you go.
快点 不要死
Come on!
拜托
快点
Hey,I know I'm not supposed to come over here or anything,
嘿 我知道我不该来这里的
but I want to talk to you,and I think you owe me that.
但是我想跟你说 我觉得是你欠我的
You owe me. That's what I think.
你欠我的 这就是我想说的
Listen,I'm sure your sister didn't mean what she said.
听着 我相信你姐姐不是真心这么说的
So,how do you make this work?
你是怎么做到的
Like,how do you juggle a girlfriend
你是怎么骗你女朋友
and a son with guys like me?
和你儿子 然后跟一个我这样的人在一起的
Well,there aren't a lot of guys like you.
像你这样的人并不多
Thanks,Teach.
谢谢 你的教诲
No,not... I mean,it's not a pattern.
不 不是的… 我想说这不是一个传统
Are you gay?
你是同性恋吗？
I can make it work with Melinda,and I really want to.
我可以跟梅琳达重新开始 我真的想重新开始
Well,good luck with that.
那祝你好运
Don't... Can you... What are you fucking doing,man?
不要… 你搞什么鬼？
That's not why I came over here.
我来这里不是为了这个
- Milo... - What am I,some sort of forbidden fruit?
- 麦洛 - 我是什么？是某种禁果吗？
- No. - Or,like,some sort of...
- 不是 - 还是某种…
What am I,like,a blow-up doll? What am I to you?
我是什么 充气娃娃吗？你觉得我是什么？
I treated you terribly. I know that. But...
我对你很不好 我知道 但是…
It's not because I don't care or because...
不是因为我不在乎 或者因为…
...I don't respect you...
我不尊重你
...or because I don't love you.
或者因为我不爱你
It's because I'm a big pussy. That's it.
而是因为我是个胆小鬼 就这么简单
I'm just a huge,pathetic pussy.
我只是个超级可怜的胆小鬼
I could never be you.
我永远也不能像你那样
You can crash on the couch,if you want.
要是你想的话 你可以睡沙发
Did you,by chance,read my script?
你有没有偶尔看过我的手稿？
Yeah.
看了
And?
然后呢？
It's great.
很不错
I'll definitely give it to my agent.
我一定会给我的经纪人的
Once again,this is the 528
又一次 这是528路公车
leaving Nyack for Port Authority Bus Terminal.
离开奈亚克去往港务局公共汽车总站
I would do anything to take back what I said.
为了收回我所说的 我愿意做任何事
For what it's worth,I'm sorry.
不管代价如何对不起
I love you.
我爱你
I screwed it up.
我把一切都搞砸了
I do that a lot,I guess.
而且非常糟糕
It's kind of my thing.
都是我的错
But I get it.
但是我明白了
Dad just...
爸爸只是…
...saw a way out.
找到了出路
I guess you did,too.
我想你也是
I'm not scared anymore.
我不再害怕了
I finally get it.
我终于明白了
See you later.
再见
Breathe,breathe,breathe. You're okay.
呼吸 快呼吸 你没事的
Are you okay?
你没事吧？
You're okay.
你没事了
All right,say something. Just say something.
好吗 快说话 随便说说
- I'm okay. - You're okay.
- 我没事 - 你没事了
You're okay,Jesus. You're okay.
你没事了 天啊 你没事了
Breathe,you're okay.
呼吸 你没事了
You're here.
你来了
I'm here.
我来了
You're here.
你来了